214.
Everyone on the invitation about fire chief, Mr. Christianelman.
Heavenly Father, we are thankful for you in the way you provide for us in the
process of this.
As you be with this meeting tonight, that you've got the discussion.
Give the council a wisdom as they make decisions for the meeting.
So your name would be great.
Thank you.
Thanks, folks.
For Republican but I'm scared of personal experiences.
For five points list.
Much to approve, Senator.
Hi.
Perfect.
James.
Hi.
Six.
Eight.
Twenty-twenty-four.
Reign.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Hi.
Peace.
Good.
All right.
Seven.
Contract amendment with a place-our-AI for annual subscription in the amount of $17,850.
Eight hundred and fifty-dollar.
Hith.
I guess.
This is just counter to amendment.
The original contract for place-our-AI did not have their 5% annual increase in it.
So it took it from $70,000 to $70,000 in the dollars.
and to give you an idea of what it does,
you should have two packets with very professional labels at the top.
That just gives you how many visitors we have at the days,
and then it has times, most people were there,
they're average times, where they came from,
and where they went to afterwards.
It's some spooky big brother stuff,
but it's really cool.
I'm still laughing at the professional labels coming at,
sorry.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
I forgot to put the titles on there,
so I was like, we have a label maker, right,
and we started packing up.
So I think the goal with this was when Amanda was still here,
she wanted to use it to not only show where people went
and how the floods affected our communities,
but then for tourism and for economic development,
for businesses if they wanted to look at some numbers.
And I talked to Tyler, he liked the idea,
we could maybe try to work out some sort of subscription service
with our local businesses,
that we could run these analytics for them,
25 bucks a month, or something, whatever works for them,
just to try to recap some of them when we do that.
Can we do that with the confidential?
Yeah, all of this data already is confidential as is.
It doesn't give you any numbers, names, houses,
anything like that just gives you zip codes.
Okay.
Which I think the information is very neat, you know what I mean?
Then we already talked to talk about it not being like if you're setting through shut-off like if you locate and shut-off it doesn't have those on either
It doesn't grant so the way it works is
When you download apps and the first time you open it's like hey, can we track your location that they partner with those companies to get that data?
Even though not everybody
uses that they do have an algorithm. They plug numbers into to then give you the numbers and
From the testing we've done it's fairly close. We did an event at the library that we did our numbers versus theirs and it was close
And then I use we do them with MLTE place at the Coleman and they're they're pretty there. Motion to approve
It's like
I am GIS annual subscription
Contract for work or management and approve
Clean from fiscal year 24.5 and amount of $15,000 there
This is a word or system we
We looked at a couple different ones. This one was the cheaper one
Militate to actually track where like first quarter weeks. We can actually
Put it on that map and it'll track with those one or like some of those two we want those to go to
We can actually publish those where where we have one of the links are road closures or
Anything on there with our with our GIS system. We can actually publish that as we get into it
It wouldn't be that to begin with what we could publish were those it's just
It's just to help us keep track of better management of what we're having those issues and we're going to go back to so we're not for getting dry-wise
So it came
This one was 13,000 design G90s was 13,000 plus a
$2,000 implementation fee and that's for a yearly subscription and then a 5%
Increase saver year after that
I was gonna ask that question
Because yeah, because that guy just said that they forgot to add that. Yeah, thank you. Yeah, you bet the other one we went to
The maintenance eggs is one of we looked at and it it the first quote that gave us was over 100,000
And then they came back and it was 26,000
480 but the difference in that was when they had limited number of access users to that this I'm GIS
It's unlimited users we can actually use it for our maintenance program also on vehicles
You can actually put those on the GIS map at OPC and
mechanics, you use that if you wanted to do that also.
Do we have a GIS person?
Yes, sir.
Did.
Yep.
Catherine, you're name?
OK.
So you know, I kind of vision like Derek briefly talked about.
So you know, you get a lot of bigger cities,
and you know, you scope their website, different things.
So they have their GIS.
They actually have a map.
This is like, we're aware of all these water links.
And the ones in red, or the big links to ones in blue,
or the smaller links of our way, or the we just get to this
time-aligned, or super-ish use, remember?
Because that's how you guys, as a board get called a lot.
Hey, you know about this water link over here.
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you kind of,
you guys can look at the map.
See, yeah, we're aware.
We can put street stuff on your also.
We're working on street.
Then good thing about this is you can add, as they close out those
workholders.
They can actually attach pictures to it that they can take from that
actually put back on our GIS system of, you know,
the repair they actually made, you know, actually
what's in the ground.
I had a question.
I really didn't protect the estimate of something you said about the
repairs and roads.
They're still rocked there.
I noticed there was one on Main Street right in front of
some room, one on 22nd, that had a water leak.
Did you get it repaired?
You put the rock in, that was there for a week or two.
And then you came back and you kind of sealed it.
It's not a permanent repair to look like, but it's on the
solid-group one.
Yeah.
And so some of the places we have that have been cut out for
six months or a year or two years at a rock.
If we go back to those and do that same type of thing,
the germ patch, we're actually working on some of those right now in
southeast, the repair and some concrete roads like that.
But we can do our patches.
The one on, you know, we do need to give it a little bit of time to settle,
otherwise it's just kind of settle when you're back to the reading
of ways, but like the one on 20 second.
Well, I meant like something like in the North West,
and then just down from that one on 20 second on the B Street,
for some sections that have been cut out and rocked back.
I'm assuming it's because there was the road was bad.
Then cut it out to do some repairs, but it's still rocked.
Can we go back and do that with those rocks for the whole water?
Yeah.
That's what we're looking at.
You know where they are.
I'm not specifically talking about where you look at.
There are, like I said, we, they have been doing something that
no they entered your patch around today working with it.
Which we have a list that we work through.
We can get on asphalt.
Some of them, the dirt patcher work on, some of it doesn't, you know, the dirt patcher.
It's hard to get to your three inches plus with the dirt patcher, but the thicker ones,
you know, we get hot asphalt.
And we have a list, but I mean, if there's one that you guys get a call on a lot,
let us know what I mean.
We can go up to this.
don't feel where there's like grass growing up. Maybe we need that stuff that's growing up.
Yeah, rock, winter, wild. So I thought if we could do that with those.
Some of those maybe on roads that we have something else that else is scheduled for work to do.
I do know a couple that we have other work. We're going to do this to be able to go and make a patch on it.
If we're going to actually take part in that else, I don't know.
How can I tell you I'll stop my head either?
I have to look back, but I'll do that. I'll get it to you.
Thank you.
All right.
Now I can get else straight ahead of them.
The Ponder claim for civil litigation.
And amount of 5,293 dollars in 70 bucks.
Yeah, it's good evening.
Trust these. This is for expert review report fee.
We're Dr. Liu from 7 on 2731-2824.
If you remember, we have this 300,000.
That was approved by the Council on 9 to 2008 for it.
Expert with this cost and this civil litigation.
The current balance is 15,765 dollars in 30 cents.
If this is approved, then it'll leave a balance of 10,471 dollars in 55 cents.
So this is on the civil litigation.
Most to approve.
Thank you.
Perfect.
5.
James.
Can I do a new business of any, which it represents is posting this agenda.
11 staff report.
Well, trustee community announcements.
13.
This meeting will be continued.
From the Council of favors.
Reconvenient staff, from the purpose of executive session.
Have the completion of the regular meeting of the Marama MIPFA.